https://yunda.com.au/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Who we areOur website address is: https://yunda.com.au/journal.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsCookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWho we share your data withHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Your contact informationAdditional informationHow we protect your dataWhat data breach procedures we have in placeWhat third parties we receive data fromWhat automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user dataIndustry regulatory disclosure requirements
Find Us DRIVING DIRECTIONS
Bruce Hwy M1 headed North (exit 244 Mary Valley Tourist Dr)
Turn LEFT onto Old Bruce Hwy (towards Imbil) 0.3kms
Turn LEFT onto  Middle Creek Rd (through Federal) 2.5kms
Turn RIGHT onto Anderson Rd (steep hill) 0.7kms
Turn LEFT into 179 Anderson Rd (number on gate post).
PLEASE ring from front gate 0414345897
AIRPORTS
Sunshine Coast Airport MCY near Maroochydore is a 45 minute drive South of us.
Brisbane Airport BNE  (depending on traffic and time of day) is 1.5 hour drive South of us.
BUS & TRAIN SERVICES
Refer to Translink Journey Planner for details
Pay an Invoice
About Us YUNDA Stead is an eco-centric homestead offering life & work experience in sustainability, ecology, climate education, permaculture / biodynamic / nutritional agriculture as well as music, art, bodywork, and meditation retreats in the beautiful Noosa Hinterlands of Sunshine Coast region in Queensland Australia.
We have majestic vistas of the surrounding Noosa Beach region and the northern end of the Sunshine Coast hinterland. There are six peaks visible from our front entry including: Mount Cooran, Pinbarren, Cooroora, Mount Boulder, Tinbeerwah, and more…
Our 50 acre property is a third natural rainforest, a third regenerated native forest, and a third grassland with orchards, gardens and amenities. It’s been naturally organic since 1984 following 40 years as dairy pastureland, 40 years as a banana plantation, and a timber harvest in 1909.
We try to sustainably re-purpose and thoughtfully  leverage all our available resources to grow… through the efforts of helpers we create, through the generosity of supporters we are better able to thrive. Want to help?
Social
NewsletterSearch
Search for:
Search
CategoriesCategories
Select Category
Beach  (2)
Bees Apiary  (2)
Brett  (4)
Cooroora  (1)
cow  (1)
dog  (1)
Farm Animals  (7)
Fauna  (1)
Fences – Pens  (1)
Flora  (3)
Friends  (6)
Garden  (3)
General  (133)
goat  (1)
growing  (2)
Helpers  (5)
Hiking Trails  (2)
Jaffa  (3)
map  (1)
mountain  (1)
Natural  (5)
Nick  (6)
Permaculture  (1)
Pets  (3)
plants  (2)
Property  (1)
Storms  (3)
Structures  (9)
Sunset – Sunrise  (3)
Tools – Equipment  (1)
Trees – Orchard  (6)
Vistas  (7)
Weather  (6)
Website – Journal  (1)
Archive Archive
Select Month
May 2020  (1)
May 2019  (1)
February 2019  (1)
January 2019  (6)
December 2018  (5)
November 2018  (9)
October 2018  (7)
September 2018  (8)
August 2018  (7)
July 2018  (5)
June 2018  (3)
May 2018  (4)
April 2018  (11)
March 2018  (5)
February 2018  (3)
January 2018  (7)
December 2017  (6)
November 2017  (5)
October 2017  (4)
September 2017  (5)
August 2017  (6)
July 2017  (8)
June 2017  (4)
May 2017  (7)
April 2017  (6)
March 2017  (20)
February 2017  (5)
January 2017  (1)
November 2016  (1)
Follow @YUNDAeco
Social Share Buttons and Icons powered by Ultimatelysocial
